https://www.hamptonrovers.com.au/privacy-policy/

Your rights to privacy
Hampton Rovers Amateur Football Club Inc. understand the importance of protecting your right to privacy and have therefore prepared this statement to help you understand how we aim to protect the privacy of your personal information.
In this document we outline what details we keep about you and why we need these details.
The new Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000 amends the Privacy Act (from 21 December 2001) to include laws that regulate the way private organisations, like Hampton Rovers AFC, handle personal information, including very sensitive information.
The Act contains 10 National Privacy Principles that regulate, among other things, how organisations collect, store and protect the quality of personal information. Also, how these organisations should use and share personal information with other organisations. The National Privacy Principles form part of all our procedures and policies and the way personal information and details are administered.
There is a summary of the National Privacy Principles at the end of this communication.
What personal information will Hampton Rovers AFC keep about me?
Hampton Rovers AFC collects personal information from clients and other associates to assist in providing our range of products and services. The type of personal information we collect about you may include your name, address, telephone number, fax number, email address, company and/or business information and details and other details appropriate to the products and services Hampton Rovers AFC provides.
Hampton Rovers AFC collects personal information when users use the Hampton Rovers AFC website to lodge their personal details, resume, company details and information, and when users change or update any of these details, or if users send Hampton Rovers AFC documents containing personal information.
Risks of using the Internet
You should note that there are security risks in transmitting information via the internet. You should assess these potential risks when deciding whether to use our on-line services. If you do not wish to transmit information via the Hampton Rovers AFC website, there are other ways in which you can provide this information, such as by mail, telephone or on-site visit.
Collection of browser information
When you browse the Hampton Rovers AFC website, our service provider logs the following information for statistical purposes:
your server address;
top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, etc.);
the date and time of your web-site visit;
the pages you looked at;
the documents you down-loaded;
the previous site you visited; and
the type of browser you used.
We will not try to identify users or their browsing activities except, in the event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider’s logs.
The Hampton Rovers AFC website is ‘cookie’ free, which means we will not send you any unsolicited information after you have accessed our website. We will only record your e-mail address if you send us a message. It will not be added to a mailing list unless specifically requested by the user.
Why does Hampton Rovers AFC need my personal information?
The personal information Hampton Rovers AFC collects about you is used to correspond with you and to provide you with other products and services from Hampton Rovers AFC.
If you choose not to provide your personal information, it may mean that we will not be able to provide these services to you.
There are other organisations that are connected to the services we provide to you and which may have access to your personal information. They are:
Member and affiliated organisations of Hampton Rovers AFC
Web development companies – organisations contracted to develop and maintain the Hampton Rovers AFC website.
Auditors and Regulators – organisations that ensure Hampton Rovers AFC is complying with legislation and contractual obligations.
Can I see the personal information Hampton Rovers AFC has about me?
Under the National Privacy Principles, you have a right to know what information Hampton Rovers AFC holds about you, and you are entitled to see this information to ensure it is correct. To obtain this information, please contact Hampton Rovers AFC to ask for your personal details. The Privacy Act gives limited circumstances in which some or all access to this information may be denied. If this applies to you,Hampton Rovers AFC will explain this to you when you ask for your information.
How can I contact Hampton Rovers AFC?
If you want further information on how Hampton Rovers AFC handles personal information, or if you want to discuss a possible breach of privacy, please contact Hampton Rovers AFC in one of the following ways:
Write to:
Hampton Rovers AFC
PO BOX 134
HAMPTON VICTORIA 3188
Or Email us via the Contact Us page.
If you are unsatisfied with the resolution of any questions, you can refer the matter to your Privacy Commissioner.
Summary Of The National Privacy Principles
Hampton Rovers AFC is bound by National Privacy Principles We will abide by the National Privacy Principles at all times.
Collecting information
We will collect personal information (where reasonable and practicable) directly from you. We may at times collect your personal information directly from other sources.
Using and sharing information
Hampton Rovers AFC will use your personal information to provide our services relevant to you. This is known as a ‘primary purpose’. If we need to use your personal information for another reason, or secondary purpose, like a marketing campaign, we will ask your permission to do so. If we are unable to get your permission before sending our communication, we will give you the opportunity to opt out of any future direct marketing campaigns at the time of mailing to you.
Keeping information accurate and up to date
Hampton Rovers AFC will ensure that the personal information we collect to provide our products and services to you is accurate and complete. We will do this by ensuring that you have the opportunity to advise changes in personal details at all times.
Keeping information secure
Hampton Rovers AFC will not misuse or change your information without your knowledge. We will not share your information with anyone who doesn’t have authority to see your information. To make sure of this, we will regularly audit access to the systems that support Hampton Rovers AFC and make sure that other organisations we deal with have Privacy policies adhering to the National Privacy Principles.
Sensitive information
Where we collect sensitive information, we will only use it for providing Hampton Rovers AFC products and services to you. We won’t use it for any other purpose or share it with anyone else without your permission.
Club Legal Documents
Authority to conduct raffles – Updated 2019
Senior Ladder
PosClubW%Pts1Hampton Rovers00.0001Marcellin00.0001Mazenod00.0001Monash Blues00.000View full ladder
Latest News
185
Club
2020 Annual Report + AGM Wrap
The Hampton Rovers AGM was held Monday evening to sign-off on what has been...
339
Club
Notice of 2020 Hampton Rovers AGM
The 91st Annual General Meeting of the Hampton Rovers Football Club will be held...
188
Seniors
Pre-Season Training is back!
As Covid-19 restrictions continue to ease, we welcomed the return of Pre-Season Training for...
To Top
